<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Income on Relaxed Income</title>
    <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/tags/income/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Income on Relaxed Income</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.relaxedincome.com/tags/income/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Alternatives for Indian Sona Masoori Rice &amp; Availability 🔥</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/best-alternatives-for-indian-sona-masoori-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/best-alternatives-for-indian-sona-masoori-rice/</guid>
      <description>Indian cuisine boasts a rich tapestry of flavors and textures, with rice playing a central role in a myriad of delectable dishes. While Sona Masoori rice has been a popular choice for ages, there exists a treasure trove of other rice varieties, each offering its unique attributes and enhancing the culinary experience. In this extensive blog post, we delve into the best alternatives to Sona Masoori rice, exploring their diverse applications in beloved Indian rice dishes, such as pilau rice, curd rice, biryani, spiced rice, and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Act of working in exchange for an income vs alternate methods.</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/act-of-working-in-exchange-for-an-income-vs-alternate-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/act-of-working-in-exchange-for-an-income-vs-alternate-methods/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to generating a consistent income, there are two types of income sources to consider – passive income and non-passive income. Understanding their differences can help you decide which income source to pursue.
Non-Passive Income aka Employment Non-passive income is earned from investments that require time and effort to maintain. Examples of non-passive income include:
Wages from a job : This when you work for someone and get paid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Money Not Friends Reversed</title>
      <link>https://www.relaxedincome.com/make-money-not-friends-reversed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.relaxedincome.com/make-money-not-friends-reversed/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to building wealth and achieving financial success, your network can play a pivotal role. Your friends, in particular, can provide valuable opportunities, resources, and support that can propel you towards your goals. In this post, we will explore how you can leverage your friendships to enhance your financial prospects and create a path to wealth.
Collaborate on Business Ventures One of the most effective ways to leverage your friends is by collaborating on business ventures.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
